<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hardware Category</string>

    <string name="student_name">Aaron Alejando Reynoza Valdez - 25-0712-2015</string>

    <string name="back">Back</string>

    <string name="Exit">Exit</string>

    <string name="desktop1">CyberPowerPC - Gaming Desktop - Intel Core i9-9900K - 16GB Memory - NVIDIA RTX 2070 - 1TB SSD - Black
        Take out the competition with this CyberPowerPC gaming computer. The Intel Core i9 processor and 16GB of RAM boost efficiency, 
        and the NVIDIA GeForce RTX graphics card produces stunning visuals to bring game environments to life. 
        This CyberPowerPC gaming computer has a 1TB solid state drive for your favorite titles and DLC.
    </string>
    
    <string name="desktop2">CyberPowerPC - Gaming Desktop - Intel Core i9-9900K - 32GB Memory - NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2080 Ti
        - 3TB HDD + 1TB SSD– Black The Syber Forti series represents the ultimate in PC gaming.
        It is a Liquid-Cooled base Super Full-Sized Tower gaming desktop designed
        with only the latest and greatest gaming technology and future expandability in mind. You can fill it up with all of the upgrades
        to meet your needs while still have ample airflow to keep the system cool. 
    </string>

    <string name="desktop3">CyberPowerPC - Gaming Desktop - Intel Core i9-9900K - 16GB Memory
        - NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2080 Ti - 4TB HDD + 500GB SSD - Black Experience fluid gaming with this CyberPowerPC Syber Cube desktop computer.
        The 16GB of memory let you multitask across several programs at once, and the 500GB SSD loads applications and Windows 10 at high speeds.
        This CyberPowerPC Syber Cube desktop computer features an Intel Core i9 processor for quick execution of complex tasks and commands.
    </string>

    <string name="desktop4">HP - OMEN Obelisk by HP Desktop - Intel Core i7-9700 - 16GB Memory
        - NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1660 Ti - 1TB Hard Drive + 256GB SSD - Shadow Black Front Bezel/Dark Chrome Logo
        HP OMEN Obelisk by HP Desktop: Play graphically intense games with this HP OMEN Obelisk desktop computer. You can easily store large
        amounts of media and other data on the 1TB hard drive and install games and programs on the 256GB SSD for fast access. 
    </string>

    <string name="desktop5"> HP - Gaming Desktop - Intel Core i5-8400 - 8GB Memory - NVIDIA GTX 1060 - 1TB HDD + 256GB SSD - Black
        HP Pavilion Gaming Desktop: Play the latest computer games with this HP Pavilion PC. The 3GB NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1060 graphics
        card smoothly displays vivid details, while the 2.6GHz Intel Core i5 and 8GB of DDR4 RAM provide speed to minimize loading times.
        This HP Pavilion PCs 1TB 7200 rpm hard drive lets you access files quickly.
    </string>

    <string name="pc1">LG - gram 17 Laptop - Intel Core i7 - 16GB Memory - 512GB Solid-State Drive - Dark Silver
        Windows 10 operating system
        This laptop is compatible with Windows 10.
        8th Gen Intel Core™ i7-8565U mobile processor
        Ultra-low-voltage platform. Dual-core, four-way processing provides high-efficiency power to go.
        The Intel Turbo Boost technology delivers dynamic extra power when you need it.
    </string>

    <string name="pc2">Dell - G3 15.6 Gaming Laptop - Intel Core i7 - 16GB Memory - NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1660Ti - 512GB SSD
        Windows 10 operating system
        Brings back the Start menu from Windows 7 and introduces new features, such as the Edge web browser that lets you mark up web pages
        on your screen.
        9th Gen Intel Core i7-9750H mobile processor
        Low-voltage platform. Powerful six-core, twelve-way processing provides blazing-fast performance when you need it most.
        The Intel Turbo Boost technology delivers dynamic power on demand.
    </string>

    <string name="pc3">Apple - MacBook Pro 15.4 Laptop - Intel Core i9 - 16GB Memory - AMD Radeon Pro 560X - 512GB Solid-State Drive - Space Gray
        Features
        9th generation 8-core Intel Core i9 processors
        Brilliant Retina display with True Tone technology
        Touch Bar and Touch ID
        Radeon Pro 560X graphics with 4GB of video memory
        Ultrafast SSD
        Four Thunderbolt 3 (USB-C) ports
        Up to 10 hours of battery life*
        802.11ac Wi-Fi
    </string>

    <string name="pc4">Microsoft - Surface Pro 6 - 12.3 Touch-Screen - Intel Core i5 - 8GB Memory - 128GB Solid State Drive (Latest Model)
        - Platinum
        Windows 10 Home
        Youll experience fast start-ups, a familiar yet expanded Start menu, and great new ways to get stuff done. And with automatic
        updates enabled,
        you get all the latest features and security hassle-free.
        Whisper-quiet fanless cooling system
        Included with the i5 model.3
        Create on screen
        Using Surface Dial (sold separately) and Surface Pen (sold separately).
    </string>

    <string name="pc5">Samsung - Notebook 7 Spin 2-in-1 15.6 Touch-Screen Laptop - AMD Ryzen 5 - 8GB Memory - 256GB Solid State Drive
        - Black Garnet
        Windows 10 operating system
        Windows 10 brings back the Start Menu from Windows 7 and introduces new features, like the Edge Web browser that lets you markup
        Web pages on your screen.
        Ryzen 5
        Enjoy high application performance and smoother gaming experiences with AMD Ryzen 5 processors, with machine intelligence,
        multitasking capabilities and efficient architecture with up to 6 cores and 12 processing.
    </string>

    <string name="key1">HyperX - Alloy Core RGB Wired Gaming Membrane Keyboard with RGB Lighting
        Enhance your in-game performance with this HyperX Alloy Core RGB gaming keyboard.
        Its soft-touch keys are equipped with anti-ghosting functionality to prevent accidental keystrokes,
        and the dedicated media controls provide quick access to frequently used functions for seamless operation.
        This HyperX Alloy Core RGB gaming keyboard is housed in a reinforced plastic frame for maximum stability.
    </string>

    <string name="key2">HyperX - Alloy FPS Pro Wired Mechanical Gaming USB Keyboard - Cherry Red MX Switch
        Match your challengers shot for shot with this HyperX Alloy FPS Pro mechanical gaming keyboard.
        Versatile lighting options let you game with confidence, and the Cherry MX mechanical keys offer solid, tactile response.
        This HyperX Alloy FPS Pro mechanical gaming keyboard is compact in size so you can easily take part in tournaments.
    </string>

    <string name="key3">Logitech - G413 Wired Gaming Mechanical Romer-G Switch Keyboard with Backlighting - Silver
        Connect this Logitech mechanical gaming keyboard to your desktop computer, and keep up with the action of your PC games.
        Backlit keys let you battle it out even during late-night gaming sessions, and Romer-G switches ensure fast responses
        at the stroke of the key. This Logitech mechanical gaming keyboard is programmable to easily meld with your gameplay.
    </string>

    <string name="key4">Logitech - G513 RGB Wired Gaming Mechanical Romer-G Tactile Switch Keyboard – Silver
        Stay in the game with this Logitech RGB mechanical gaming keyboard. The 1ms response rate delivers fast reaction for keeping up
        with battles or chasing down treasure, while the mechanical switches provide a satisfying feel and actuation.
        LIGHTSYNC technology means you can customize the lighting on the keyboard to suit your playing style. Combining
        a full-length palm rest with a classic metal chassis, this Logitech RGB mechanical gaming keyboard is made for serious gaming support.
    </string>

    <string name="key5">Logitech - Orion Spectrum G910 Wired Gaming Mechanical Romer-G Switch Keyboard with RGB Backlighting - Black
        Maintain full control of your gaming commands with the customizable, illuminated keys on this Orion Spectrum mechanical gaming keyboard.
        Connect the unit to a smartphone or tablet to display in-game information when you need a second screen.
        Anti-ghosting protection keeps the Orion Spark mechanical gaming keyboard from freezing up during intense gaming sessions.
    </string>

    <string name="mouse1">Apple - Magic Mouse 2 - Silver
        The all-new Magic Mouse 2 has been enhanced to deliver more comfort and functionality than ever before. It includes a built-in
        rechargeable
        lithium-ion battery that charges fast, lasts about a
        month or more between charges, and eliminates the need for disposable batteries. With the included Lightning to USB cable, you can charge
        your device and automatically pair it with any Mac.
    </string>

    <string name="mouse2">Logitech - MX Master 2S Wireless Laser Mouse - Graphite
        Darkfield Laser Tracking works on virtually every surface, even glass
        This technology creates a micromap of the smallest possible details to allow tracking on shiny surfaces and clear glass
        (at least 4mm thick).
        7 buttons
        Provide access to frequently used commands and functions for powerful control.
    </string>

    <string name="mouse3">Logitech - M510 Wireless Laser Mouse - Silver/Black
        Quickly input commands with this Logitech M510 910-001822 mouse that features laser technology for precision tracking on most surfaces.
        The Logitech unifying receiver allows simple wireless connectivity.
        Laser technology
        Enables smooth, ultrafast tracking on most surfaces.
    </string>

    <string name="mouse4">Microsoft - Sculpt Comfort Wireless Optical Mouse - Black
        Microsoft Sculpt Comfort H3S-00003 Wireless Mouse: This ergonomic, right-handed mouse features a scooped thumb design
        and a 4-way scroll wheel for easy Web browsing. Blue Track technology allows accurate use across a wide range of surface types.
        4-direction scroll wheel
        Scroll wheel can be used to scroll both vertically and horizontally.
    </string>

    <string name="mouse5"> Insignia Bluetooth Mouse Black
        Utilize your mouse more efficiently with this Insignia six button Bluetooth mouse.
        It incorporates forward and backwards buttons as well as a scrolling wheel and left and right buttons,
        and the dpi button lets you change sensitivity on the fly. This Insignia six-button Bluetooth mouse is wireless so that you can use it
        anywhere thats in range.
    </string>

    <string name="monitor1">LG - 27UL600-W 27 IPS LED 4K UHD FreeSync Monitor with HDR - Silver/White
        Enjoy a stunning LED display with this 27-inch LG monitor. The 4K UHD resolution and VESA DisplayHDR deliver vivid scenes
        to keep you captivated
        by your favorite shows and movies, and IPS technology maintains consistent colors at various viewing angles. This LG monitors
        Radeon FreeSync matches your graphics cards frame rate for a stutter-free experience.
    </string>

    <string name="monitor2">LG - 32 UltraFine IPS LED 4K UHD FreeSync Monitor with HDR
        Work on professional creative projects with this 31.5-inch LG UltraFine 4K monitor. Nano IPS and VESA DisplayHDR 600 color technologies
        provide accurate display of image details for precise color grading and efficiency in various post-production tasks.
        The Thunderbolt 3 interface of this LG UltraFine 4K monitor supports daisy-chaining, high-speed data transfers and laptop charging.
    </string>

    <string name="monitor3">Samsung - UJ59 Series U32J590UQN 32" LED 4K UHD FreeSync Monitor - Dark Gray/Blue
        Enjoy enhanced viewing with this 32-inch Samsung monitor. The widescreen display lets you browse multiple windows
        and applications comfortably, and the upscaling technology boosts the clarity of lower resolutions to match UHD-level picture quality.
        This Samsung monitor uses AMD FreeSync technology to maintain a consistent refresh rate for smooth visual performance.
        Supporting a billion shades of color, the UJ59 delivers incredibly vivid and realistic images.
    </string>

    <string name="monitor4">BenQ - EW3270U 32" HDR LED 4K UHD FreeSync Monitor - Metallic Gray
        Watch 4K and HDR content with this 32-inch BenQ LED monitor. Its Brightness Intelligence Plus Technology detects ambient lighting
        conditions
        for optimal adjustment of display settings while preserving the cinematic quality of videos.
        This BenQ LED monitor has preset low blue light settings for multimedia, web-surfing, reading and office modes to support eye safety.
    </string>

    <string name="monitor5">Samsung - 34 LED Curved QHD FreeSync Monitor – White/Silver
        Enhance your viewing experience with this 34-inch Samsung Thunderbolt monitor. Its 21:9 aspect ratio lets you multitask
        by browsing various windows and applications side-by-side, and the curved design reduces eyestrain while providing maximum immersion.
        This Samsung Thunderbolt monitor uses AMD FreeSync technology to deliver smooth frames for gaming and video playback.
    </string>
</resources>
